Guide to Bradford College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00252
Cubberley Education Library
Bradford College (formerly: Bradford Junior College; formerly: Bradford Academy)
1926-1979
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00252
87 item(s)
Located in Bradford, Massachusetts. Founded as Bradford Academy in 1803. Became a women's college in 1836. Name changed to Bradford Junior College in 1932. Became coeducational and changed name to Bradford College in 1971. Given authority to grant a bachelor's degree in 1974. Closed in 2000.
Junior colleges; Massachusetts; Women's colleges -- United States
- Bradford Academy, 1926-1933; 6 item(s) Catalogs for 1926/27, 1928/29-1932/33
- Bradford Junior College, 1934-1972; 70 item(s) Catalogs for 1934/35-1937/38, 1939/40-1972 Suppl. Curriculum 1948/49
  - Bradford Junior College Bulletin, [1935]-January 1966; 14 item(s) Bulletins for [1935], 1943-1944, 1959-1961, 1963, 1965-1966
  - Bradford Junior College: Program of Studies, [1938/39]; 1 item(s) pamphlet rec'd Feb. 1939
  - Bradford Junior College: The Haverhill Gazette, March 9, 1953; 1 item(s) Newspaper
  - Bradford Junior College: School Issue, May 1960; 1 item(s)
  - The Bradford Graduate and College Transfer: A Survey, 1959-1973; 7 item(s) Surveys published: 1959, 1963, 1967-1968, 1970-1971, 1973
  - Bradford Junior College: A report to Secondary Schools and Colleges, 1963-1965; 2 item(s) Reports for 1963 & 1965
  - Bradford Junior College: Admissions Newsletter, October, 1967; 1 item(s)
  - Bradford Junior College: Independent Study at Bradford, 1966-1969; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1966 & 1969
  - What's New at Bradford, 1970-1971; 1 item(s) brochure of changes for 1970/71
  - Bradford Junior College: Notice to Juniors Accelerated Admission for September 1971, 1 item(s) Poster for 1971
- Bradford College, 1972-1979; 11 item(s) Catalogs for 1973-1979
  - Bradford College: Institute of Urban Studies, 1972-1974; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1972 & 1974
  - Bradford College: Independent Study at Bradford, [1974]; 1 item(s) Bulletin rec'd April 1974
  - Bradford's Open Curriculum, [1974]; 1 item(s) Bulletin rec'd April 1974